leedsbeckett.ac.uk 2016-12-04

# Privacy Policy - Leeds Beckett University

* * *

### Privacy Statement

This privacy statement covers the information services relating to the website provided by Leeds Beckett University (Leeds Beckett) as www.leedsbeckett.ac.uk (the Leeds Beckett website). 

The purpose of this statement is to inform users of the Leeds Beckett website about what information is collected about them when they visit this site, how this information is used, any disclosure to third parties and the ways in which users' privacy is protected.

### Confidentiality and security

Leeds Beckett University takes your privacy seriously. Any information you provide will be held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Your personal details are not normally disclosed to any third party.

However, under certain circumstances, we may need to disclose your personal details to a third party so that:

  * they can provide a service you have requested
  * we can fulfil a request for information

Any information about you that we pass to a third party will be held securely by that party, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, and used only to provide the services or information you have requested.

You have a right to request a copy of your personal details used for such purposes to check the accuracy of the information held. 

If you wish to do this, please write (explaining that your interest is in the website www.leedsbeckett.ac.uk) to the:

Data Protection Officer 

Leeds Beckett University 

Calverley Street 

Leeds 

LS1 3HE

### Information we collect from visitors for our own use

We collect several kinds of information from visitors to www.leedsbeckett.ac.uk depending on the part of the site being visited: e-mail enquiries, student recruitment, e-mail addresses, site usage information and, in a few cases, personal details such as your name and postal details if you order publications/documents to be sent or register for a service provided by the University (for example, the student accommodation service).

### Where we store your personal data

The data we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, amongst other things, the provision of support services. 

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Leeds Beckett will take such reasonable steps as necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

You should be aware that, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.

### Enquiries comments and questions

If you send an enquiry by e-mail to a specific contact listed on the Leeds Beckett website, this will be passed to the relevant section of the University so that they can fulfil your information request.  
If you sign up for a subscription e-mail service, we will hold the information you have provided for as long as you require access to the service requested. 

If you inform us that you wish to cancel a subscription we will remove you from our mailing list and your details will be deleted from our records.

### Site usage information and cookies

Cookies are pieces of data created when you visit a site and are stored in the cookie directory of your hard drive. They generally do not expire at the end of your session. Cookies do not contain any personal information about you and cannot be used to identify an individual user. They are used to help you when you return to a website. 

For example, they may enable you to return directly to a particular part of the site by 'remembering' where you last accessed. If you choose not to accept the cookies (by setting your browser to reject them), this should not affect your access to the majority of facilities available on our website.

### Where cookies are used

### Linking to other sites from the Leeds Beckett website

The Leeds Beckett website contains many links to other sites, to help you find the information you need. 

These may be 'official partners' of Leeds Beckett or other third parties with information likely to be of interest and relevance to those using our website. Leeds Beckett is not responsible for the privacy practices of the organisations that operate these other sites. 

You should be aware of this when you leave www.leedsbeckett.ac.uk and, if concerned, read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.

### Advertising

We may use advertising on parts of the public (Internet) or private (Intranet access only) parts of the Leeds Beckett website. 

No information will be passed to such advertisers or their agents about those using the Leeds Beckett website unless such users 'click through' to a specific advertiser's site and offer their personal details directly to the advertiser.

### Changes to this privacy policy

If this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page so that you can remain aware of any information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with third parties.
